<resources xmlns:xliff="http://schemas.android.com/tools">

    <string name="paid_reason">Why isn\'t ACrypto free?</string>
    <string name="paid_reason_description">
        Remember all those cool startups you used that were free but then they were acquired,
        shut down and now don\'t exist anymore? It\'s because free apps don\'t make money,
        and therefore can\'t survive
        \n\n
        Someone builds a cool, free product, it gets popular, and that popularity attracts a buyer.
        The new owner shuts the product down and the founders issue a glowing press release about
        how excited they are about synergies going forward. They are never heard from again.
        \n\n
        Whether or not this is done in good faith, in practice this kind of exit event is a
        pump-and-dump scheme. The very popularity that attracts a buyer also makes the project
        financially unsustainable. The owners cash out, the acquirer gets some good engineers,
        and the users get screwed.
        \n\n
        To avoid this problem, avoid mom-and-pop projects that don\'t take your money!
        You might call this the anti-free-software movement.
        \n\n
        If every additional user is putting money in the developers\' pockets, then
        you\'re less likely to see the app disappear overnight. If every new user is costing 
        the developers money, and the app is really taking off, then get ready to read about 
        those synergies.
        \n\n
        I love free software and could not have built my app without it. But free 
        services are not like free software. If your free software project suddenly gets 
        popular, you gain resources, testers, developers and people willing to pitch in.
        If your free app takes off, you lose resources. Your time is spent firefighting and 
        your money all goes to the nice people at Linode.
        \n\n
        So if you want ACrypto app to survive, please support it and become a paid member.
        
        \n\n
        ACrypto is mostly free where you can see different prices of crypto currencies along 
        different exchanges, coins list. Getting arbitrage between currencies, setting alerts for 
        price drops and maintaining portfolio across is not. Why?
        \n\n
        Because this is not a venture-capital funded startup. It\'s bootstrapped! We don\'t 
        have any external funding on purpose. The problem with so many venture-capital funded 
        startups is that their investors force them to grow fast in user base without making any 
        money in the first few years, to then sell out to BigCo (e.g. Google, Facebook) for a few 
        million dollars, then write a blog post about their incredible journey, then either shut 
        the app down, or fuck over their users by filling the service with ads.
        \n\n
        That sucks, right? I don\'t get that. I don\'t like that.The reason people do that 
        because they\'re trying to make a quick buck. I get it. I\'d love to too. But the
        odds of actual success are very low in that realm.
        \n\n
        So I\'d rather go for higher odds of success, try to make money on day one, and not 
        make a billion dollars but just make good money to live off. Maybe I can hire a few people
        then later on. Maybe I even get funding later, but then it should be money that\'s 
        really necessary. Maybe I\'d actually get acquired later too. But it\'d have to be 
        good for the users in the first place. And there shouldn\'t be the extreme high growth 
        trajectory which will then fuck over my users.
        \n\n
        The challenge of going this way is that you can\'t offer everything for free, like 
        Facebook or Google or any other funded startup does. You have to get money somehow. I 
        could make money in sneaky ways like selling your user data, but that\'d suck and 
        honestly it wouldn\'t make that much money at this scale. So the fastest way is 
        simply asking you, as a user of this app, for money.
        \n\n
        Remember, right now this app is mostly me on a laptop coding my way through life. I 
        love it and it\'s super fun but it also means that if I can\'t make any money with
        it I have literally no money and I\'ll have to get some desk job and this app won\'t 
        exist.
        \n\n
        So if you like what I do, please support this app and become a paid member.
    </string>
</resources>
